We are Juice=Juice!
As announced a few days ago,
Juice=Juice has decided to have a new member join the group.
So, I would like to immediately call out the new member.
Mifu Kawashima, please come in!
Please welcome her!
Please give a big round of applause.
Please come in, Mi-chan.
Cute.
Now, please introduce yourself to everyone.
I'm Mifu Kawashima, a new member of Juice=Juice, from Kyoto, a first-year high school student, 15 years old.
Nice to meet you.
Wow Rias.
Wow, Rias.
The cheers are amazing,
Wow, that's great.
You know what?
Oh, man.
I'm so happy.
Today is the first time for you to perform at Nippon Budokan,
Did you get a sense of what it was like after your debut?
It was my first time to perform on such a big stage as Nippon Budokan,
I'm really nervous,
I will do my best to perform with the members of Juice=Juice as soon as possible,
I'll do my best to perform with the members of Juice=Juice as soon as possible,
Are you okay?
You're good.
Please give me your support.
I can't help it if you're cute and cuddly,
I'm sure you're probably wondering about this too,
I would like to announce Mifumi Kawashima's member color.
Here it is. Here you go!
Jean!
Amazing!
Everyone works so fast.
It's red, but Mifuchan's member color is,
Cure Red!
Oh no!
I was hoping you all would do Fenlight,
That's great!
Shall I choose one or the other?
One or the other.
One.
Just once.
Let him memorize it while he's at it.
Wow.
It's so beautiful.
Super beautiful.
So cute.
Now, when you've calmed down, can I ask you again?
Yes, I can. Well, when I heard the color red, at first I thought it was very unexpected,
But now that everyone is wearing red like this,
I hope that you will continue to...
Go for it!
Go, go, go!
I am so happy to think that you will wave red penlights at our concerts from now on.
I'm so happy to think that I'll be able to wave a red penlight or wear a T-shirt at concerts from now on. I'm looking forward to it!
Thank you very much.
I think it's really fresh, though,
Miki Kawashima will accompany us from the July concert,
We are planning to start full-fledged activities around fall,
I hope you will all wave your red penlights again,
Please look forward to it.
I am looking forward to seeing you all again. This time, I'm going to be accompanied by Rin Kawana from Angerme and Ichika Arisawa from Juice=Juice.
This time, we will be presenting with these two, so please bear with us until the end.
Please bear with me until the end.
Now, we are finally approaching the end of our spring tour.
This tour is the 10th Anniversary of Juice- Juice.
10th Anniversary.
10th Anniversary. Yes, it's the 10th anniversary concert,
I personally think that this tour has brought us closer together,
I think I have grown as well.
I think it was wonderful.
This tour seemed to fly by so fast,
We started in March,
How do you feel about it?
I also realized how fast time flies through the tour.
And on June 21, we will be holding the Angstrom Concert 2023!
LOVE Akari Takeuchi Final Live
LOVE From Angerme with love will be held at Yokohama Arena.
This is the live where Ms. Takeuchi will graduate,
I will do my best to show the current position of Angerme to the best of my ability.
So please give me your support.
Please watch this video first.
Please take a look!
It's about time to take you to the end of the pillar.
Your words, your gestures, your hearts that shake.
You know what? Listen to me.
Let me play with the shell of a camshiro with my fingertips.
"It's been a boring spring," you say.
I'm so embarrassed, Gruss, that I pretend I didn't hear you.
It's the best I can do.
I can't remember who I was seeing last year.
The girl you were with last year... she seems happy now.
I've always been you.
Sakurazakura, sakurazakura, sakurazakura, sakurazakura, sakurazakura, sakurazakura
I've been with you for a long time.One, at singing distance from each other.
It's gonna end like this.
Don't dream too much, you're being mean.
Sunday rain
Take me back to my place... where the flowers are in bloom for the next seven minutes.
I can't fall in love with someone who knows I'm in love with you. I can't do it.
I'll be your girlfriend if you fall in love and spill it.
Why are you kidding me? I don't want it.
Subtitles: Enjoy.
What have you been up to?
I've been switching jobs.
You're always meeting new people.
Expectations, hopes, seasons of confusion.
I'm sorry, we're as far apart as ever.
I'm just going home.
It's more like that.
But I love it.
Frustratingly lonely
Seven minutes away from honesty
I can't even behave right
I can't do it, I can't do it
It's not that I love you
Like I don't even love you
A crush that only you can feel
Thank you for watching!
Spring, summer, unrequited love, fall and winter, our paths have crossed
And finally you realize
I can't wait, I can't wait, I'll be your girlfriend
I'll be your true love
Look, look, look, look. Petals from the window.
That wasn't a joke.
Words and music by Miho Nakajima
Thank you for everything. I'm rooting for you too.
Rin Kawana of Angerme and Ichika Arisawa of Juice=Juice present "Halo! Stay!
From here, we'd like to talk a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer in a quick tempo!
It's going to be rainy season soon, so what's your fashion style to protect yourself from rain?
Carry a jacket.
Ichika-chan has a sense of absolute pitch, what is the most interesting sound you've heard recently?
Rin Kawana's voice
What is the best word in English for Juice=Juice right now?
Family
Tell us the origin of your name, Ichika Arisawa.
One and only one flower
Hello! Project's 25th anniversary this year, what song would you like to perform on your violin?
Juice=Juice's "Be honest and sweet
There are a few things that really caught my attention.
What do you mean by carrying a jacket to protect yourself from the rain?
I'm the type of person who doesn't go outside with an umbrella.
Do you mean as a substitute for an umbrella?
I sometimes carry my violin instead of an umbrella.
I don't want my violin to get wet, so I sometimes carry it like a raincoat for my violin.
Can't I just use an umbrella?
Umbrellas are fine, but there are times when I just don't want to carry an umbrella.
I see.
I understand.
You also said that my voice has interesting sounds because of my absolute pitch.
I heard a lot of Rin Kawana's voice today.
I was thinking how wonderful your voice is.
There are times when we say "yes" in sync, aren't there?
At that time, the blending of your voice and mine was so comfortable that I wanted to sing with you.
I want to sing with you.
I hope it's okay to say that, I want to sing with you.
Thank you very much.
Questions for Ms. Kawana after the VTR
Halo! Sta.
We're so promising.
Earth is a place where the law of the jungle is the law of the jungle.
Use your power and feel the world
The Beast of Love June 14th Onsaiyo
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't
I'll never kiss Benchova
I couldn't lose, not even to you.
Pride Bright July 12 Onsayo
Everymance, Mr. Destiny's Traveler
Let's anticipate coincidences and conjure up miracles
Beyonds New Single
Seek Me, Destiny's Traveler
Now Onsaiyo
No one can stain it, the night sky is watching over us
Beyonds New Single
Yozora no Yume wo Kigaeru Yozora ni Nau Onsaiyo
Hallo! Sta.
Next, I would like to ask Rin Kawana a question.
It's the season of frogs, Rin Kawana-chan's favorite!
What kind of frogs are you interested in right now?
It's a strawberry toad.
It's been about two and a half years since you joined Angeleum.
What do you think is your weapon?
Her eyes.
13 years ago this time, Yumemiru 15 was released.
From your point of view, what does this song mean to you?
It is a very important song.
What is the point of today's fashion?
The one-piece dress given to me by Mr. Shinkoku Ryori.
Which song from Hello! Project's history would you like to perform?
Morning Musume。 14's "There's No Substitute for You".
I told you what I'm interested in.
Which song from the Project's history would you definitely want to perform?
I'd like to hear this song.
The lyrics of the song are very powerful.The lyrics of this song, "There's No Substitute for You," are very powerful.
And the dance is very unique.
But I think it's a difficult song to sing alone.
I have a longing to perform it with various people on some occasion.
And one more thing, Rin Kawana's weapon
My weapon
I often get compliments on my eyes.
I'm often told by the members that I have strong eyes.
So I answered that I think it is my weapon.
I feel like I'm being sucked in by the power of your eyes the whole time I'm standing next to you.
I'm glad.
Hello! Stay tuned for more after this!
This is Masashi Natsuyaki. Here we go, Hello Kitchen. This time, we have this member here.
Yes, this is Yumeno Kishimoto from Tsubaki Factory. I will do my best to cook delicious food.
I look forward to working with you.
Yes, thank you very much.
Now, teacher, what would you like to cook today?
Yes, today, I'm going to make a face clam.
Oh, wow. It looks difficult.
This is a dream one, isn't it? I heard it as a request.
I'm listening.
I really love mangai, and I think it's the No. 1 dish that I can eat without thinking about it even when I'm on a diet.
I love mangai so much that I go out to eat it 3 or 4 times a week,
I love it so much.
I really want to make this dish, so I made this request.
So let's get started.
What shall we do first?
First of all, we need to cook rice and meat.
Certainly.
First of all, I would like to remove the sinews and oil from the chicken.
I'd like to do something like that.
There's water in it, so I'll wipe it up with paper.
There's this kind of fat.
Do you know what it is?
I have no idea.
This is excess oil.
He wants to get rid of it.
It's between the skin and the meat.
I never thought about that.
We tend to get it under the belly too.
This is the extra oil.
The skin itself is not so bad.
The skin is fine.
That's what I mean.
I didn't know that.
I didn't know.
This one.
I can't have this.
I took all of them.
I cook them together in the rice.
I don't mind so much.
This is the empty part.
It's hard here, so I want to drop it here.
I want to avoid right here.
I want to hold it down, and I want to drop it.
This is for me.
Fight me.
Be careful.
Fighting.
This isn't muscle training, is it?
You should be able to pull it all the way through.
If it's too hard, you can use kitchen scissors.
That's fine.
Or scissors.
Slide it off.
Let's take it.
I'll slide it in.
I'm sure.
That's it.
You're listening to me.
That's the image.
I'm not here to cook, I'm here to tell Mr. Tsunahiki.
It's too big. Cut it in half.
There's a dividing line here.
When I cut chicken, I always put the skin side up.
Should I do it the other way around?
Skin down is better.
I see.
Is it easier to cut?
The skin always ends up on the bottom.
I tend to cut the flesh first.
Hold the knife up for the skin.
Then, can I cut the meat first?
Can I cut the meat first?
Hold the knife very high.
Stand up really high.
Yes, sir.
Pull back.
Put some rice on top.
That's right.
You can push this one in first.
Let's put it in once.
Can we use chicken?
Use it.
But then...
I'll just cut it like this.
You can cut it
It doesn't matter if it's shredded.
If it's sharp, it's sharp.
But it's a good cut.
Okay, now that you've cut it in half...Then I could cut it in half.
Then...
Chop up the ginger.
20 grams of ginger.
The peel should be on the back of a spoon or something.
I see.
Use this one.
Not this one.
This one.
What?
Amazing.
Crunchy, crunchy, crunchy.
Oh, wow.
Easy
Crunchy, crunchy
Wow!
Amazing!
Really!
Is it okay if I don't take too much?
Yes, it's fine.
To be honest, it doesn't have to be this beautiful.
It's so clean.
If you wash it, it'll be fine.
Then...
Next...
I also need garlic.
Garlic
Coarsely chopped
Yes, sir.
I'll use a clove of garlic.
Me.
Shredded.
You know, chopped...
I'm...
I'm really bad at it.
I'm not very good at it.
When I was making sauteed burdock root...
Yes.
You know...
Vegetables...
Yeah.
Just by cutting them...
I'm exhausted.
Yeah.
Strength
Oh, no.
No, that's right.
Like when you're in the forest.
Yeah.
Oh!
The source of the sauce.
Yeah.
You make green onions and stuff like that, right?
In small pieces.
Yes, I do.
I'll do it today.
Okay.
Yuuchan.
Wait a minute.
Pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre-pre
It's difficult.
Really?
Are you sure you can handle this?
Yeah, it's fine.
This one too.
Here you go.
That was quick.
You all right?
That's great.
Oh, okay.
Ginger, too.
About the same.
Yes, ma'am.
This one.
The one you cook with rice.
That's right.
Then the same amount of ginger.
Yes, sir.
I'll cut it to size.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Your hands are good.
Yes, sir.
You cut it very quickly.
Yes, yes.
Now it's time to make the rice... but first...
Can I put them in the bag to release their aroma? Yes, sir.
Do you have any special moves? Special move?
Special moves? Like a stick up.
No? You mean like a smack? That's what I mean.
Ouch. - Oh, are you sure about this?
What? What do you mean? What does it mean?
Try putting it in the bag. Wow, great.
You put it in the leeks, right? Yes, I did.
Does it give off an aroma? Yes, it gives off an aroma.
It's just a tablespoon. A little less at first.It's just a tablespoon. A little less at first.
A little bit, really. Wow, the green onions look delicious.
Yes, the green onions look delicious. I won't touch them.
Really? You're on your own.
You're going to put them in the rice, too? Of course.
You'll put them all in.
Wow, they're so beautiful.
Looks so good!
With the heat off.
It gets burnt easily. It's matured with the oil.
It's browning nicely.
Put the rice in here.
Here's a point you don't see.
We don't wash the rice.
Why don't you wash it?
If you wash it, it gets soggy.
By frying, oil coats each grain.
And when it's cooked, it becomes soft and fluffy.
It's the same with hilaf, deep-fried tofu, whatever.
Put it all in.
Once the rice is cooked, the garlic and ginger won't burn.
When you fry the rice in the frying pan.
After it's cooked, you can only make it into a stir-fry.
Please turn off the heat.
And when you fry the rice here, you put it all in the pan.
It smells good. It smells good.
It smells good, it smells good, it smells good.
Smells good.
Flatten the whole thing.
Then we put the chicken on top of it.
Is there a direction? On the skin.
When the skin starts to pillon, spread it out and stretch it.
When you fry and cook this kind of rice.
The amount of rice is equal to the amount of water.
If you put the rice in this way, the seasonings will not be mixed.
So here's sake and soy sauce, both 2 tablespoons.
Mix them a little bit.
I see.
So the flavor won't be mixed up?
That's right.
Is it okay this way, too?
Put it on the rice cooker.
How long will it take to cook?
It depends on the standby power.
I'd say about 40 minutes.
Okay.
It's okay if you cook it fast.
That's good. I'm the type of person who can't wait for rice to cook.
I tend to cook rice quickly.
That's all for now.
It's going surprisingly well.
I'll continue next time.
Good afternoon.
Bon appétit!
Hello, fresh from the kitchen.
How are you cooking these days? I haven't been cooking lately, so I'm hoping to get better at it.
I've been wanting to get better at cooking. How about you, Icika?
I also want to work hard at making sweets, since the members of juice=juice often bring us bread and sweets.
I also want to work hard at making sweets.
I want to eat them next time.
Hallo! Sta!
Project has a lot of songs.
Project has a lot of songs,
Project has a lot of songs, but there is one lyric that I think touched my heart,
Project has many songs, but the lyrics in the song "All is the Power of Love" by Morning Musume。 Project has a lot of songs, but the lyrics of Morning Musume・・Project's song "All is the Power of Love" that really touched me was the phrase "All is the Power of Love,
The lyrics are very powerful and clear,
I think the lyrics are very beautiful and make you want to believe in the power of love.
How about you, Icika?
I like Morning Musume。 19's "Hey! Unfair Baby" lyrics as a whole,
I often listen to it on the train or something,
I often listen to it on the train. Before work.
Please watch the VTR. Please watch the VTR.
Presentation of lyrics that touched my heart
In this corner, we will present the lyrics of the songs of Hello!
Project's songs and talk about the charm of the lyrics. Project's songs and talk about their charms.
This week, I, Yoshiho Sato, will be presenting.
Here it is.
Tokime Kirakira Kanae wa
I want to do this, I want to do that, I want to do this, I want to do this, infinite power!
Then I'll show you for real, I won't let go of your hand
This is a lyric of the song "Koshitan-tatan" by Beyonds.
Is it called "C part"?
We're all in it together
It's the part where everyone gets excited before the last part.
It's the part where they get excited.
From the moment I heard the lyrics
It's my favorite part in "Koshitan Tatan".
There's a scene where a magical girl really transforms, right?
It's called "Henshin Bank" and it's like that.
The clothes change, the hair changes color...
Her hair changes color.
Her hair changes color, and accessories are attached.
And so on and so forth.
I can imagine the scene of the transformation
I can imagine that scene.
Isn't it so cute?
It's so cute.
I thought it was really cute.
Like, "Let's show it off.
It's kind of cute in a light-hearted way.
I won't let go of your hand.I'll never let go of your hand
When I'm performing
I don't want to let go of the hands of those who are watching me.
I feel like I can do the same.
You hold hands with yourself all the time.
I think I'm a singer who can believe in myself.
You have a sparkling, glittering, glistening feeling.
I don't know what it is.
It's not the sparkle of a fluffy girl.
I felt a little bit of glitz and glamour.
When I was singing...
The lyrics make you feel like you're being moved.
I think it's really good.
The more you sing this, the more confident you'll be.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Everybody's transforming
I'm transforming
I'm changing I'm changing I'm changing I'm changing I'm changing I'm changing I'm changing I'm changing
Yes, that's how it goes... sparkling lyrics.
Beyonds has a lot of sparkling lyrics, so please give it a listen!
See you next time!
Hallo! stay!
Rin Kawana from Angerme and Ichika Arisawa from Juice=Juice.
and Chika Aoi of Juice=Juice.
Halo! STE!
Angerme will be on June 14th
and Juice=Juice will release their new single on July 12.
will be releasing their new single on July 12!
I would like to introduce each new single in a few words.
Yes, that's right!
Yes, I used the word "cohesion" to describe Angerme this time.
We've been working as a 10-member group for more than a year now.
This will be our last single as a 10-member group since Mr. Sakiyoshi is graduating.
I hope you can see the cohesiveness of the group after more than a year of activities with the same members.
As for Juice=Juice, I would like you to pay attention not only to the music but also to the dance performance.
Angerme will be released on June 14, and Juice=Juice on July 12.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
This will be our last song!
Let's enjoy it until the end!
I don't have anything good to say
I'm about to say something to myself, but then I stop
It's not too late
Let's take a detour and go home
Even when I don't want to
There's another universe for me
Ride the positives
I'll be fine as long as I travel
In a world of whimsy
Even if it's not kindness
I'll rise again and again with the voice inside
Morning, evening, days are full
In the midst of the plastic, I wonder what it's like Every Day
I'm happy because I have a heart to enjoy
Rejected web step, cried chan step
Filled up in front of each hour
Wink is the most important
Cheerful, isn't it? Aren't you smiling?
I'll be like a woman
Isn't that how it's supposed to be?
Wink.
To be loved.
But I'm just so insecure.
I can't help it. I'm so insecure. I can't help it.
Yeah, I know. "I love you.
It's all up to me.
I just have to remember to weigh the scales.
It's too early to start acting like you can afford it.
I'm not ready yet.
I'm going to push forward again and again
Into the stormy sea
Take a good night's sleep and make it to the center seat
Someday in Hawaii, go-ho-bee
Everyday I dream even if I don't care
I'm not afraid 'cause I've got it
I'm nervous I'm nervous I'm nervous I'm nervous I'm nervous I'm nervous I'm nervous I'm nervous
But not only that, I'm on fire
Weekend Sometimes I'm in the right spirit
Simple, Tonri Addition.
I'll do it. I can see it.
That's how it's supposed to be.
Thank you for watching.
No matter what I do here, as long as I'm me.
Eternal Courage will bloom again and again.
I'm off!
It's enough to fill you up
The most important thing is
Is your energy and your smile.
What does simple look like?
It's going to be "I'm so happy"!
That's how it should be.
Today, something good happened.
This is Halo! Sta.
It's time for us to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
Angerme's new single "Ai no Kedamono" will be released on June 14.
Ai no Kedamono Dousumonjo" will be released on June 14!
Both songs have powerful lyrics.
Please listen to them!
And on July 12, Akari Takeuchi's solo
single "V I gotta go" will also be released on July 12!Single V I gotta go will also be released!
Please check it out too!
Yes, and Juice=Juice will release a new single on July 12!
A new single will be released on July 12!
It is a double A-side single including "Pride Bride"!
The lyrics of the song can be shared by many people, so please pick it up and listen to it!
Please pick up a copy and listen to it!
Juice=Juice will be performing at the Topping Base in Kyoto 2023 on June 3.
Toppin Base in Kyoto 2023 on June 3.
Yes, and Angerme will be performing at
Angerme Concert 2023 Big Love
Akari Takeuchi Final Live
Angeurum will hold "From Angeurum with love" at Yokohama Arena!
Yes, we would like to send off Ms. Takeuchi with a smile.
We are looking forward to seeing you at the venue!
Hello! Project members will appear more and more on this channel!
Project members every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
Please subscribe to the channel!
This time we have Rin Kawana from Angerme and Ichika Arisawa from Juice=Juice.
Juice=Juice's Ichika Arisawa!
Goodbye!